<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Family</title>
    <link>https://cloudfamily.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloud Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudfamily.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - April 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/april2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/april2020/</guid>
      <description>Isidora Katanic - @IsidoraKatanic    About Isidora Katanic is born in former-Yugoslavia, grew up in the Netherlands since the early 90&amp;rsquo;s and moved to Switzerland in 2017. She is on the Management Board at the Swiss IT firm make it noble and the co-founder of the event management company districtUP, organizing IT community conferences like Experts Live Europe and Experts Live Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - May 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/may2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/may2020/</guid>
      <description>Vaibhav Gujral - @vabgujral    About Vaibhav Gujral is a seasoned cloud architect with close to 14 years of experience in designing enterprise-class applications. Born and brought up in India, he completed his Bachelor of Engineering degree in 2006 after which he started his career with Infosys as a software engineer. The first breakthrough in his career came in the year 2010 when he got an opportunity to work closely with Microsoft product teams to onboard new customers onto Microsoft Azure (it was Windows Azure back then).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - June 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/june2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/june2020/</guid>
      <description>Lisa Clark - @lisaattheedge    About Lisa Clark lives in Dundee, Scotland with her Maine Coon Kizzi and works for Dell Technologies.
Lisa is a Business Development Strategist for EMEA focussed on the Azure Stack portfolio. Lisa works with Microsoft, Speciality sales teams within Dell and SME&amp;rsquo;s to bring the right people together to in order to support customers in realising their Microsoft Hybrid Cloud goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - July 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/july2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/july2020/</guid>
      <description>Mert Yeter - @m3rtyeter    About Mert Yeter is a software engineer with 15 years of experience in .NET and Microsoft technologies. He completed his Bachelor of Engineering in 2005 and has a master&amp;rsquo;s degree focused on Linux. He has also 3 years of experience in Cisco Contact Centre products and implementations. Mert is very passionate about technology, both software and hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - August 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/august2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/august2020/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Barona - @HmsBarona    About Hugo Barona is one of the community leads of Cloud Lunch and Learn, helping this initiative to enable everyone to learn about the Cloud, while enjoying their lunch or break. The initiative has been going great, connecting people all over the globe to attend sessions, to collaborate and deliver sessions, and helping to buildits ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - September 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/september2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/september2020/</guid>
      <description>Gwyneth Pena S. - @madebygps    About Gwyneth Pena is a Cloud Consultant, content creator, and Microsoft Azure MVP.
Before deciding to work for herself, Gwyn was a Cloud Engineer at an Energy startup and was responsible for all the company&amp;rsquo;s Azure Infrastructure.
She is an advocate for diversity and inclusiveness in the field and creates content not only on skills she&amp;rsquo;s learned, certifications she&amp;rsquo;s studying for, but also shares her story and tips that helped her get into the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - October 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/october2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/october2020/</guid>
      <description>Marc Duiker. - @marcduiker    About Marc Duiker LOVES serverless, developer communities and creative coding! He works for Xpirit as a Lead Azure Consultant and loves working with event-driven architectures, and serverless technology such as Azure Functions, Durable Functions, Cosmos DB, and various messaging products.
He is an Azure MVP since 2019 and regularly blogs and vlogs about Azure Functions &amp;amp; Durable Functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - November 2020</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/november2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/november2020/</guid>
      <description>Shabaz Darr - @ShabazDarr    About Born in the Bradford in the North of the UK and been there ever since! I have recently joined Netcompany as a Senior Infrastructure Consultant based in there Leeds Office. I have two children, Zoya (10) and Mikaeel (6) and a better half in my wife, Reema (she will kill me if I tell you her age ha ha ha).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Blogs</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/blogs/azure_blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/blogs/azure_blogs/</guid>
      <description>Pixel Robots - A Blog about Microsoft Azure and Sysadmin stuff...  Gregor Suttie - Azure Greg  Thomas Thornton - Blogging all things Microsoft Azure  Joe Carlyle - WedoAzure  Sam Smith - Learning and sharing Azure architecture tips with DevOps  David O&amp;#39;Brien - Cloud For The Win!  Dwayne Natwick - The Journey To The Cloud Continues  Chris Pietschmann - Build5nines.com  Alan Kinane - Azure Alan  Jack Tracey - Cloud and Networking  Vaibhav Gujral - Cloud Architect  Pete Gallagher - Pete Codes  The Azure Guy - Martyn Coupland  Kirk Ryan - A blog about advanced Azure data services  Adil Touati - Azure, DevOps and Kubernetes  Elan Shudnow - Azure Cloud  Sam Cogan - All things Azure and Cloud  Thomas Maurer - Azure Cloud &amp;amp; Datacenter Blog by Microsoft Cloud Advocate  Mark Scholman - Azure &amp;amp; Azure Stack blog  Azure Stack Community Blog  Tobias Zimmergren&amp;#39;s thoughts on tech  Mark Patton - Azure Cloud &amp;amp; DevOps  Vukašin Terzić - AzureIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/projects/podcasts/azure_podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/projects/podcasts/azure_podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Cloudskills.fm CloudSkills.fm is a weekly podcast with technical tips and career advice for people working with cloud-native technologies. This show is for developers, IT pros, or anyone making a career move into the cloud. Episodes will be short and to the point and will regularly feature experts who share their experiences.
This show is hosted by Mike Pfeiffer, a twenty-year tech industry veteran, entrepreneur, Pluralsight author, and Microsoft Azure MVP. If you enjoy the show and want more tips delivered to your mailbox every week, subscribe to CloudSkills Weekly at https://cloudskills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure YouTube Channels</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/youtube/azure_youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/youtube/azure_youtube/</guid>
      <description>Azure Advent Calendar
The Azure Advent Calendar YouTube Channel. Here you will find around 75 videos all about Azure. Look out for the next advent for more awesome content.
 Sam Cogan
A YouTube Channel from MVP Sam Cogan focussed on learning Azure. Includes the Azure Snippets series, a collection of short, to the point tutorials focussed on working with Azure.
 Mark Scholman
A YouTube Channel from MVP Mark Scholman focussed on learning Azure Stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archetypes</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/archetypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/archetypes/</guid>
      <description>Using the command: hugo new [relative new content path], you can start a content file with the date and title automatically set. While this is a welcome feature, active writers need more : archetypes.
It is pre-configured skeleton pages with default front matter. Please refer to the documentation for types of page to understand the differences.
Chapter To create a Chapter page, run the following commands
hugo new --kind chapter &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;/_index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Champion - January 2021</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/january2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cloud_champions/january2021/</guid>
      <description>Deepthi Goguri - @dbanuggets    About Deepthi Goguri is hard working, passionate SQL Server enthusiast, well-organized team player and is a proud mother of two children.
Deepthi moved to united states from India to pursue her master&amp;rsquo;s in computer technology from Eastern Illinois University.
Deepthi is currently working as SQL Database Administrator in Administrative Office of the Courts, Kentucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown syntax</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/markdown/</guid>
      <description>This page is a shameful copy of the great Grav original page. Only difference is information about image customization (resizing, add CSS classes&amp;hellip;)
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: Writing content for the Web is tiresome. WYSIWYG editors help alleviate this task, but they generally result in horrible code, or worse yet, ugly web pages.
Markdown is a better way to write HTML, without all the complexities and ugliness that usually accompanies it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-104 - Azure Administrator</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-104/</guid>
      <description>AZ-104  Links you may find useful Here is a list of links that you might find useful when studying for your Azure exams. Feel free to create a pull request to add more.  Skyline Academy:
https://courses.skylinesacademy.com/p/az-104 Scott Duffy:
https://www.udemy.com/course/70533-azure/  Microsoft Learn Resources Below you will find a list of free resources from Microsoft on their Microsoft Learn site.
 Administer infrastructure resources in Azure (12 Modules)
https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/paths/administer-infrastructure-resources-in-azure Architect storage infrastructure in Azure (7 Modules)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-303 - Azure Architect Technologies</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-303/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-303/</guid>
      <description>AZ-303  Links you may find useful Here is a list of links that you might find useful when studying for your Azure exams. Feel free to create a pull request to add more.
 Skyline Academy:
https://courses.skylinesacademy.com/p/microsoft-az-300-certification-azure-architect-technologies Scott Duffy:
https://www.udemy.com/course/70534-azure/  Microsoft Learn Resources Below you will find a list of free resources from Microsoft on their Microsoft Learn site.
Architect great solutions in Azure
https://docs.microsoft.com/learn/paths/architect-great-solutions-in-azure Architect network infrastructure in Azure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-304 - Azure Architect Design</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-304/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/az-304/</guid>
      <description>AZ-304  Last updated: 06/03/2020
 Links you may find useful Here is a list of links that you might find useful when studying for your Azure exams. Feel free to create a pull request to add more.
 Skyline Academy:
https://courses.skylinesacademy.com/p/az-301 Scott Duffy:
https://www.udemy.com/course/az301-azure/  Microsoft Learn Resources Below you will find a list of free resources from Microsoft on their Microsoft Learn site.
Need links
 Exam registration page https://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DP-300 - Administering Relational Databases on Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/dp-300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/study_guides/azure/dp-300/</guid>
      <description>DP-300 Exam Resources Study Guide  Plan and Implement Data Platform Resources (15-20%)
Deploy resources by using manual methods
 deploy database offerings on selected platforms - https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-database/sql-database-paas-vs-sql-server-iaas configure customized deployment templates - https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-database/sql-database-resource-manager-samples?tabs=single-database apply patches and updates for hybrid and IaaS deployment - https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/sql/virtual-machines-windows-sql-automated-patching  Recommend an appropriate database offering based on specific requirements
 evaluate requirements for the deployment evaluate the functional benefits/impact of possible database offerings evaluate the scalability of the possible database offering evaluate the HA/DR of the possible database offering evaluate the security aspects of the possible database offering  Configure resources for scale and performance</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu extra shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/menushortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/menushortcuts/</guid>
      <description>You can define additional menu entries or shortcuts in the navigation menu without any link to content.
Basic configuration Edit the website configuration config.toml and add a [[menu.shortcuts]] entry for each link your want to add.
Example from the current website:
[[menu.shortcuts]] name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fab fa-github&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Github repo&amp;quot;identifier = &amp;quot;ds&amp;quot;url = &amp;quot;https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn&amp;quot;weight = 10[[menu.shortcuts]]name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-camera&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Showcases&amp;quot;url = &amp;quot;/showcase&amp;quot;weight = 11[[menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icons and logos</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/icons/</guid>
      <description>The Learn theme for Hugo loads the Font Awesome library, allowing you to easily display any icon or logo available in the Font Awesome free collection.
Finding an icon Browse through the available icons in the Font Awesome Gallery. Notice that the free filter is enabled, as only the free icons are available by default.
Once on the Font Awesome page for a specific icon, for example the page for the heart, copy the HTML reference and paste into the markdown content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archived Virtual Events</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/virtual_events/archived_virtual_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/virtual_events/archived_virtual_events/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Events
 msHOWTO Live! #13: Traefik Proxy 101 - Tuesday 29th September - 4.00pm - 5:00pm UTC  msHOWTO Live! #12: How to Succeed with the Power of Community - Tuesday 15th September - 3.00pm - 4:00pm UTC  msHOWTO Live! #11: Datacentre Migrations and Azure Migrate - Tuesday 21st July - 5.00pm - 6:00pm UTC  msHOWTO Live! #10: GitHub, Azure DevOps, so much confusion… or maybe not? - Tuesday 26th May - 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/sitemap/</guid>
      <description>We should be careful about the references we include in the sitemap xml file, to avoid a high volume of pages included in the sitemap and consequently being indexed to Search Engines such as Google, Bing and more. Especially because we should mind about keeping the most relevant content in the top of the search engine index.
Configuration Hugo by default indexes all pages to the sitemap.
The proposal is just to include a parameter to the pages we want to exclude from sitemap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/tags/</guid>
      <description>Learn theme support one default taxonomy of gohugo: the tag feature.
Configuration Just add tags to any page:
--- date: 2018-11-29T08:41:44+01:00 title: Theme tutorial weight: 15 tags: [&amp;#34;tutorial&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;theme&amp;#34;] --- Behavior The tags are displayed at the top of the page, in their insertion order.
Each tag is a link to a Taxonomy page displaying all the articles with the given tag.
List all the tags In the config.toml file you can add a shortcut to display all the tags</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachments</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/attachments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/attachments/</guid>
      <description>The Attachments shortcode displays a list of files attached to a page.
AttachmentsBachGavotteShort.mp3(357 kb)Carroll_AliceAuPaysDesMerveilles.pdf(175 kb)adivorciarsetoca00cape.pdf(361 kb)hugo.png(17 kb)movieselectricsheep-flock-244-32500-2.mp4(340 kb)Usage The shortcurt lists files found in a specific folder. Currently, it support two implementations for pages
  If your page is a markdown file, attachements must be place in a folder named like your page and ending with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/button/</guid>
      <description>A button is a just a clickable button with optional icon.
{{% button href=&amp;quot;https://getgrav.org/&amp;quot; %}}Get Grav{{% /button %}}{{% button href=&amp;quot;https://getgrav.org/&amp;quot; icon=&amp;quot;fas fa-download&amp;quot; %}}Get Grav with icon{{% /button %}}{{% button href=&amp;quot;https://getgrav.org/&amp;quot; icon=&amp;quot;fas fa-download&amp;quot; icon-position=&amp;quot;right&amp;quot; %}}Get Grav with icon right{{% /button %}}Get GravGet Grav with iconGet Grav with icon right</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/credits/</guid>
      <description>Contributors Thanks to them for making Open Source Software a better place !
And a special thanks to @vjeantet for his work on docdock, a fork of hugo-theme-learn. v2.0.0 of this theme is inspired by his work.
Packages and libraries  mermaid - generation of diagram and flowchart from text in a similar manner as markdown font awesome - the iconic font and CSS framework jQuery - The Write Less, Do More, JavaScript Library lunr - Lunr enables you to provide a great search experience without the need for external, server-side, search services&amp;hellip; horsey - Progressive and customizable autocomplete component clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expand</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/expand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/expand/</guid>
      <description>The Expand shortcode displays an expandable/collapsible section of text on your page. Here is an example
Expand me...Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Showcase</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Azure Spring Clean by Joe Carlyle &amp;amp; Thomas Thornton  Azure Advent Calendar by Richard Hooper &amp;amp; Gregor Suttie  GitHub Actions Advent Calendar by Edward Thomson </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mermaid</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/mermaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/mermaid/</guid>
      <description>Mermaid is a library helping you to generate diagram and flowcharts from text, in a similar manner as Markdown.
Just insert your mermaid code in the mermaid shortcode and that&amp;rsquo;s it.
Flowchart example {{&amp;lt;mermaid align=&amp;quot;left&amp;quot;&amp;gt;}}graph LR;A[Hard edge] --&amp;gt;|Link text| B(Round edge)B --&amp;gt; C{Decision}C --&amp;gt;|One| D[Result one]C --&amp;gt;|Two| E[Result two]{{&amp;lt; /mermaid &amp;gt;}} renders as
graph LR;A[Hard edge] --|Link text| B(Round edge)B -- C{Decision}C --|One| D[Result one]C --|Two| E[Result two]or you can use this alternative syntax:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notice</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/notice/</guid>
      <description>The notice shortcode shows 4 types of disclaimers to help you structure your page.
Note {{% notice note %}}A notice disclaimer{{% /notice %}}renders as
A notice disclaimer
Info {{% notice info %}}An information disclaimer{{% /notice %}}renders as
An information disclaimer
Tip {{% notice tip %}}A tip disclaimer{{% /notice %}}renders as
A tip disclaimer
Warning {{% notice warning %}}A warning disclaimer{{% /notice %}}renders as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Link in New Tab</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/openinnewtab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/openinnewtab/</guid>
      <description>You can use this shortcode to open a link in a new tab.
link Name link Name </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>page test</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/children/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/children/test/</guid>
      <description>This is a test demo child page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>page test 3</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/children/children-2/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/children/children-2/test3/</guid>
      <description>This is a test 3 demo child page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raw HTML</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/rawhtml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/rawhtml/</guid>
      <description>You can use this shortcode to display HTML content on a page.
This is raw HTML, inside Markdown.
This is raw HTML, inside Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site param</title>
      <link>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/siteparam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudfamily.info/cont/shortcodes/siteparam/</guid>
      <description>siteparam shortcode is used to help you print values of site params.
For instance, in this current site, the editURL variable is used in config.toml
[params] editURL = &amp;#34;https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn/edit/master/exampleSite/content/&amp;#34; Use the siteparam shortcode to display its value.
`editURL` Value : {{% siteparam &amp;quot;editURL&amp;quot; %}}is displayed as
editURL Value : https://github.com/CloudFamily/CloudFamily/tree/master/content/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
